Guide to the Fausto Giaccone photographs and papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 2.2; (10 boxes)
  - Macondo: The world of Gabriel García Márquez, 67 inkjet prints of photographs taken in Colombia, 2006-2010 (Box 13 (Oversize), Folder 104-107)